You see these $1,000? I'm going to help
him flip this into $100,000. And his
name is David or also known as the GK
Kid where he was hand selected from
50,000 people that applied to be in this
position. And after reviewing 50,000
applications, flying to multiple
different states and after interviewing
15 different people in person, we're
left with David. So, after we decided
that we were going to choose David,
picked him up in my jet in Naples, and
now he's going to be living with me here
in Miami, where not only am I going to
teach him my whole entire training
strategy to perfection, but we're also
going to get him in shape. Yeah, I was a
little overweight, so now we're going to
get it right a little bit. So, not only
is he going to be profitable, he's also
going to get his fitness fully in check
by leading with me here, training with
my trainer, eating what I eat, doing
everything that I do. He came in as
David, but he's going to be leaving as
the G. Sounds pretty cringe, but it's
the truth. And the craziest part is
we're going to be documenting the
before, the dur, and the after of every
single position we take while we're
taking the,000 to 100,000 here on
YouTube with weekly recaps Instagram
live every single day. And we're going
to be sharing the trades live in
Telegram and WhatsApp. So, with that
being said, let the challenge begin. All
right. Good morning, ladies and
gentlemen. This is officially day one of
the challenge. How do you feel? I'm
feeling awesome. Are you sure? Yes, I
am. You look like you haven't slept. Cuz
I haven't. right now, Monday, June 9th,
7:29,
9:00 in the morning. And if you guys see
this right here, what is that? That is
our alarm to let us know for us to be
ready to enter the first trade. So,
right now, the account is at $1,000. As
you can see, we just deposited $1,000
last night. Everything is in a real
account and we are basically ready to
take the trade. So, the way this is
going to work is David is supposed to
let me know when he's ready to take the
trade and then I guide him to it. But I
said, David, let me take care of the
first trade. All right. Trust me, the
the the first trade is the most
important trade and you want to make
sure you can execute it perfectly so it
gets you out of the hole. We're risking
100%, right? Yeah. Literally 100%. It's
my money. You're good. You're you're
you're pre-rolling here, right? So,
first trade. Well, actually, the first
trade that we were going to take was
GBPND. So, GBPND, we shared it yesterday
on the live stream. And then here you
can see a perfect retest of this
neckline of the head and shoulders. We
came back up, we retested it, and we as
soon as the market opened, it just shot
straight into our takerit. We actually
never retested the area of interest, the
EMA or the round psychological level or
even the neckline. We literally just
opened and went down. So, the trade
played out. We just couldn't catch our
entry. GBP CAT on the other hand, so I'm
actually in this trade for almost $7,000
in profit. But since I've been holding
it for nearly a week, I am in draw down
because of this spread swap fees, all
[__] right? So, with you, you're
basically going to enter the same trade
as me or even have a better entry and
not be holding it for a week. So, back
to GBP CAD. It's basically exact same
trade as GBP and ZD. We basically have a
head and shoulders. Right now we are
retesting this neckline. Came back up.
Retested the EMA and now we came back
and retested it one more time. This we
anticipated yesterday on Sunday swings
on GBPNZD. So retest break right here.
Retest break and hasn't fully sold yet.
So we're anticipating to sell from this
right now. So we were actually going to
enter about 15 minutes ago. We actually
say are saving ourselves some draw down
right now. The 30 minutes shifted and
looks like we can potentially create a
right shoulder up into here. Left head,
right shoulder. And if we do get a right
shoulder up here, we'll sell up here. If
we start rejecting and start heading
down, I'll enter immediately. So, for
right now, I'm not going to enter cuz it
would actually be in draw and I don't
want to enter just cuz it's going into
my stop loss here. I'm just going to
wait out and see what it does. Euro GBP.
Right now, we are currently being a
little bit slow simply because it hasn't
gave us what we need. So, Euro GBP, the
daily time frame has a left head, right
shoulder at this area of interest, and I
need for it to fully retest this area in
order for me to have price head to the
upside. So, we haven't done that yet.
And then AUD CAD, we are approaching
this area, but we're looking for it to
sell, but we're not that interested in
it just yet. The main one right now is
GBP CAD. We're going to remain patient
until we can get an entry around 7:33 in
the morning. It's having the retest of
this kind of right shoulder area over
here. And I'm going to be waiting to see
what price action does. So now we now we
just wait. Now we just wait. This is the
part that sucks cuz you're just looking
at this shape. So we got to wait. All
right. So we're going to check back in
in 45 minutes. See what price did. See
if we enter or if we didn't.
So we're about to take our first trade
right now. And I was just telling David
that, bro, let me take the first trade.
Trust me, it's the most important trade.
And we're going to risk 100% right now.
Like like this trade is going to make or
break the whole entire account right
now. [__] it. [__] it. All right. So,
we're going to enter GP CAD after this
shift of structure. The 1 hour time
frame is a shift of structure. And now
we are having that wick retracement. All
right. Let's enter. Just to show you
guys $1,000 GP CAD trade and then not 90
lots and $1,000. That would be crazy.
We're going to start off with let's just
put two lots and our stop loss is going
to be 1.85733.
1.85733.
And all right, so you want you you can
click the sub button. Okay, tell sell.
All right, now now we do it again.
Oh, brother. Not enough, my honey. All
right, we're full margining this [__]
right now. And then let's try again, but
with a.5. And I I know some of you guys
may be asking, why don't you just enter
everything on one position? Because I
don't like to. All right, well, we're
already max margined up. All right, so
we're in, boys. We're officially in our
first position. GBP CAD. Good luck. We
did it. We haven't done anything yet.
Oh, we got Oh, yeah. We did start. Sure.
Fine. So, right now it's 7:51 in the
morning. We'll check back in in about 30
minutes, 40 minutes, and let's see what
the market's on. All right, so update. I
don't know. Yo, you Yo, you can't make
this [__] up, bro. All right, so you
can't make this up. This is the [__]
first trade right here. You literally
cannot make this up. I told you, man. I
I I got it. Let Let me Let me take this
[__] out of the out of the Yeah. Out of
the shore. No, out of the the dock. the
dock. I mean, take the ship out of the
dock and once we are in open waters,
brother, do whatever you want, man. Look
at this. This [__] alone, like if if if
right now we're up 250 bucks in this
little piece right here, this can give
us easily like four or five grand. All
right, so right now we are currently
rejecting this area exactly how we have
anticipated and other for I mean there's
really nothing else other I'm I'm so
excited I can't even speak right now.
I'm just like wow. We're up $300 [__]
dollars. Yeah. And just like that. What
the hell? Wow. This is We should have
done this a while ago, bro.
Every single day I feel the pressure
double up the work. Let's make it extra
working
like I never knew.
Yo, what's up? So, how does it feel like
to be a week into the house? Crazy. I
mean, I've changed so much stuff in my
life and learned so much stuff as well.
I mean, you saw you saw the the trait
that we took earlier. I mean, that's
just crazy. I never seen that much money
so fast in my life. Never. And that's
just the first trade. So, what was
everything you learned last week? Uh,
basically I learned like I already knew
about the trading. Uh, Alex basically
reinforced that knowledge. We learned
about necklines. We learned about
basically analyzing. We're going to
learn about points of interest. We
learned about resistance support. We
learned a lot of stuff. A lot of stuff.
And what do you think was the difference
between what you already knew and just
applying it now with Alex? You feel like
you just needed someone to give you that
boost of confidence? That's first. And
second, I mean, there's a lot of stuff
that from ignorance you don't exactly
know what to do. Alex is a really I mean
he has been like more than 6 years I
believe in the market. So I mean you can
tell that there's some stuff it's little
stuff that changes the whole thing but
you like for example trader like me I
never noticed he does. So those like
those little things that are little for
us but huge in general that he notices
and and we don't. And another goal Alex
put for you was for you to lose weight.
So how much are you weighing now and how
much do you think you're going to weigh
at the end? Um so let me let me do the
three. When I landed I was in 236. Right
now I'm on 227 and by the end of the
challenge hopefully 200 200 2 200 210.
What do you think is going to be harder?
Winning the challenge or losing point.
[Music]
Yo, hold up. Hold up real quick. Just a
trade update. Okay, I got you. I got
you.
[Music]
Trade update. And when I called you,
we're actually up 9. Like the highest
we've been was 950. 950 already. I know.
I know. So look right here. You can see
the left head, right shoulder.
Technically, we broke the neckline. We
retested that structure point and now
we're having the continuation to the
downside. So, like right now, we're up
800 bucks. We have to take a group.
That's crazy. 4hour time frame, very
strong 4hour bearish engulfing closure.
We're having the continuation of that
push. And then if the daily time frame
closes like this as a bearish daily
rejection, we should have a very strong
continuation move to the downside. I'm
I'm very confident in this trade. Set
and forget. There you go. That's what
I'm talking about. By the way, if you
guys don't know, David, how much did you
weigh? How much did you weigh yesterday?
Like 227. How much did you weigh when
you got here? 236. Oh, wow. So, you've
lost decent amount of weight. Yeah,
we're we're in a good way. We're we're
going in a good way. Cuz our our goal
isn't for David just to learn a skill
set and actually make money from it. Our
goal is for him to actually like change
his life completely monetary wise and
like physical wise. Oh, he's doing
cardio two times a day. Sauna once a
day. Both two times. Like after each
session of cardio, you hit sauna too. Oh
[__] And then on top of that, the
training with Max, you working out with
me and the diet. No, wait, wait, we we
logged in. I know. I know. Like this
like this is going to be a complete like
makeover in 30 days. Trade update.
I'm on hold with the bank. So, right now
we're down 135 bucks. You know who these
are? Who? You know the guys that wear
like the caps on the the back of their
head? Oh, I know who they are, but I'm
not going to mention it. Those guys,
they watch all the [__] I do for real.
And when they watch everything I do,
they they they try and like take my
money. They try unbalance it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, that's exactly
what they did here. So, if you see when
I enter the trade, look at this. It goes
perfectly into profit as soon as I post
it right back into breaking. And now
they think that that scares me. N
doesn't scare us. That doesn't do
anything, right? So, what we're going to
do is we're going to continue to hold.
We're going to set and forget. I said I
go about our B like if this didn't even
happen. That we didn't do it at all.
What do you mean we didn't do it? We
didn't do it. No, I mean we're going to
think we didn't to just forget it. Said
it and now we forget. Wait, what? Now we
lost it. The point is we set it. Forget
now. Trade is back at break even. This
is where people are like, "Oh, you
should have closed at $1,000." No. Trade
did not hit my take profit. I don't
close the trade cuz this trade had
potential to have more without having to
add any more risk. But for now, we just
set up forget and see what happens. GBP
CAD wants to [__] around.
and tolerated. So right here we have our
famous GBP CAD. So our goal is to hit it
right direct right there. Right there.
If we miss, we lose. We miss. We lose.
Yeah. So we have plenty of options to
choose from. All right. I'm going with
my favorite, a pink. I'm actually going
to start off with this. You going to
start out with that one? Yeah. We go
pink and go home. Okay.
Guys going to hit the wall.
He's missing all of them. I'm not even
hitting it. Mission fail. Mission
failed. Let's try and use a a different
weapon. This is This is my personal
weapon. Oh, I think I got it. Yo, that's
like right on the money. Let's see if
that did anything in real time.
Still did not. How can I forget? The
most useful gun in my collection. Shout
out to Trump [__] up the
should get the job done.
Good job. Right. Let's see if it didn't.
We're going to have to find another
city. What are you going to do?
With that being said, it didn't [__]
work. Not at all. We're going to find
another solution that'll work. Okay. I'm
going to make some phone.
I can't believe you blew the account.
I do. I'm not I'm not I'm not surprised.
Like I actually don't I love that this
happened. I'm not going to lie. You love
that this happened. Yeah. Yeah. It's a
It's part of the game. Market update.
Right now, it is currently 10:00 at
night. We have officially blown the
account. We have lost GBP CAD and we
lost GBP CAD because of [__] [__]
wick out bro. So GBP CAD we were in this
cell earlier. So after the 30 minute had
this head and shoulder shift
destructure. We then had to pull back up
into this area. We rejected from it.
This is where we at the range and it did
a little bit but um not enough. This
this is like real [__] Like this is
for real [__] This is how you know
they're watching us. It literally went
direct to my stop loss. And as soon as
it went to my stop loss, direct into
profit. So, this is literally showing
you that they're watching us. But it's
fine. It's fine. No big deal. We're not
going to get nervous. No, we got another
$1,000 in us already. We're going to use
your money now. Okay, cool.
So, I believe that this trade is still
good. I believe we just got wicked out
because of wickouts and uh that if this
4hour closes as this bearish engulfing
candlestick in the next 2 and 1/2 hours,
I am going to be interested in taking
that trade. So that's going to close at
1:00 in the morning roughly and uh we're
going to be trading London tonight. So
you could go knock out. I know you're
tired cuz you're fasting or whatever and
your cardio, but I'm going to be up
tonight for London. If we do go take the
trade, I'll wake you up. If not, I won't
make you wake up for no reason. And
we're gonna deposit another thousand
dollars right now. Just ship it right in
to show you guys. We're gonna do this
live. So, this is our brand new.
Yeah, we have uh just total deposits
one. Yeah, total deposits. $1,000 into
this. This is a brand new account,
right? So, we have $83. We're going to
deposit right now in real time. All
right. So, we just got the payment
probably what, a minute later. So, and
we have $83. But, you know what? We're
going to deposit the full,000. We're
going to have a little bit more than
$1,000. That's it. We're back in the
game. We have advantage this time. Yeah.
So, we have a $83 advantage now. So,
we're back in the game. All right. So,
for tonight's we have GP CAD, which I'm
going to be waiting for some potential
sells. We have Eurog GBP, which I'm
going to be waiting for some retest of
this area for buys. AUD CAD, I might be
interested in sells around this high.
And GBPZD, the trade is just completely
gone. So, we're actually going to put
that one at the bottom of the list. Our
main focus is still GBPC CAD. So, 10:00
at night, we're going to set and forget.
See you guys hopefully later tonight.
Later. Hopefully later tonight. If not,
tomorrow in the morning.
[__] man. Yo, give me something to
throw. Uh, give me something. Show the
cash that we know. Yeah. [__] man. This
is your fault. My fault. Yeah. Why? You
don't wake me up, man.
Oh my.
You missed out on GBP Cat. Let Let me
show you guys this [__] [__] So,
we got whipped out. So, those guys with
the hats, bro, those [__] bro.
[__] bro. Those [__]
bro. They They They did this to us. This
is an us thing right now. You understand
what's going on? Yeah, I got you. I'm
not Oh, wait. I'm actually my other
trade. I can close my other trade. I
mean, it's not that bad. Like, I'm still
up on my account, but [__] Whatever. On
the other account, we did not take the
trade. They did this to us yesterday.
Look at this. They wicked this out after
that. Gave us the perfect engulfing. And
then what happened? Exactly what I said.
Straight to our takerit. If I would have
literally just woken up for 30 seconds,
I would have just taken it from my
phone. Just taken it right there in that
spot. No, the worst part is like imagine
if we would have just not been wicked
out at the point that we would be right
now. No, no. Right. Right now, right now
the account would be at $4,000. Oh my
god. I thought, oh no. So, we missed out
on GBP CAD. Can I get any more
transparent, any more legit? You want to
know what's even crazier? People inside
of my community, they entered GBP CAD.
This person caught it. This person said,
"Bro, I flipped my account from a,000 to
4,000." If we show, for example, another
person right here, GBP CAD has fed a lot
of folks. except me. So, right here,
this dude made $973.
So, this guy made money on it. This guy,
GBP CAD, he entered it last night. He
made about $5,000. The the the person
that gives the signal or gives the trade
didn't win at all. No, no, we actually
lost. We No, you didn't work. Yeah, cuz
we we blew the account yesterday. So,
you know, it's okay. This happens to the
best of us. I feel like everything
happens for a reason. We called the
trade perfectly. Like right now, we
would literally be at the goal for we
would be passed for the goal for the
week. The goal for the week is for the
account to be at 3,000. We would have
been past that. Remember yesterday, Euro
GBP? Look at this. Euro GVP. We called
it yesterday to perfection. It didn't
come back in and retest to the depth
that I wanted to, but the move happened
perfectly exactly how I anticipated. And
look at this [__] bro. We're literally
left at the exact same spot. Look at
this. Have not taken any new positions.
This is so so much [__] But you
know, you know what? We're going to
enter a trade right now. [__] it. You
know what this is called? [__] your way.
No, this is called revenge trading. Oh
yeah. This is how you really make money.
Okay, you really make money in this
trade. All right, so this next trade
that we're going to take right now is
AUD CAD. AUD CAD. Right now, we're
having a rejection from the area of
interest. Daily time frame is
potentially creating a daily wick or a
dogee. The 1 hour is creating a little
head and shoulders pattern. So, we have
left head, right shoulder. We have an
engulfing evening star formation here.
30 minute. If we body candlestick close
below this candlestick right here, I'm
going to immediately enter that trade.
So, I'm going to be waiting for some
volume to kick in for me to enter this
trade. I'm I'm not gonna I woke up this
morning. I'm I'm I usually we would
start the video like at 7:30 in the
morning and you were asking me when are
you gonna come? I said, "Bro, dude, I
gotta just like breathe a little bit."
Dude, we called it perfectly. Everything
that we said happened and on top of
that, people caught. We're the only ones
that Yeah, we literally So now you got
to wake up, bro. I know I told you to go
to sleep, but like wake up in the middle
of the night at 3:00 a.m. I just I just
I'm going to come over here for a little
bit. So look at the chart. If the chart
like if if you would have woke up at
3:00 a.m. and you would have seen this,
you would have Yeah. Yeah, you would
have woken me up. So like wake up at
that time and if you see something just
in case in the event that I'm sleeping,
you wake me up, you automatically. Okay.
All right. So for now, let's wait for a
CAD to give us our opportunity. And
that's it.
What about heated the whole thing again?
100%. Yeah, we're going to risk 100
fucking% again right now. 100 fucking%
right now, dude. Dude, you have no like
I I I I like I don't know. Like might it
might seem funny the way they're editing
it. They make it make might might be
making it a me, but I'm actually [__]
mad. Like, I feel it like right here,
bro. Give me a massage, man. Like that?
Like that? Is that okay? Oh, yeah. Yeah.
You know what? You know what? That was
Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it.
Come on. That actually hurt. I'm not
going to lie. So, we're going to we're
going to go for a cat, dude. That's
exactly [__] Look. Look. You can't make
this [__] up, man. You can't make this
[__] up. Literally gave us the [__]
thing right now. Click it again. Click
it again. Don't sell. Sell. You almost
click buy. Sell. Sell. I was going
there. You two lots. Sell. Sell. Wait,
wait. The stop loss. Sell. Sell. There
you go. Let me click this one. 5 01.
Sell. Boom. Team work. There you go.
Yeah. So, this is a trade profit. We
should be around $3,000. So, we entered
the trade. I feel a lot better now.
We're in there. You feel better? I feel
a lot better now. All right. So, AUD CAD
sell. We are in right now. We're going
to just continue to hold this position
and we're going to completely ignore the
[__] fact that GBP CAD could have
easily given us. Look, even more. Yeah.
Literally, no. No. This shit's going to
keep going down, bro. Like it's gonna
keep plummeting to the downside, bro.
Whatever. All right. Set up for game,
guys. Oh [__] Get him. Get him.
Great update. So, right now we are my
little farm back here. So, I eat nine
eggs every single day. Since he's been
living here, he eats 11 eggs every day.
You eat How many eggs you eat a day?
Probably like four. Four. So, that's a
total of about 69 eggs. So, instead of
us continuously buying eggs, which are
very expensive, we decided, you know
what? Why don't we just make our own?
So, I got 30 chickens. We get about an
egg or two off each chicken a day.
Accommodates for all of our egg needs a
day. This one right here, this is Sarah.
What's Patunia, bro? Oh, this is
Patunia. Uh-huh. Patunia is the queen.
If you can tell her beak is crooked cuz
she got into a fight earlier and she
lays about three eggs a day. But this is
not about that right now. This is about
a trade update. It's 2:00 in the
afternoon right now. How do you think
we're in the trade? Do you think we're
up or down? I think we're up. The last
the last kind of update we were up.
Yeah. How much are we up? Um 400. Yeah,
you're so wrong. So off, bro. We're
break even. Look at this [__]
This is no [__] So right now AD CAD
we are break even literally from where
we entered went into a little we went
into draw down we almost blew the
account went into a little bit of profit
now we're on break even and what pisses
me off is GBP CAD look at that
continuing to melt beautiful bearish
moves to the downside I had an
opportunity to scale in there for sales
but honestly I was just so mad at it
that I avoided it and AUD CAD right now
the daily time frame is closing pretty
decent so we're just going to be waiting
for the daily time frame to to close for
me this is the ultimate sign of success
I have my own chickens I I have my own
gym over here, my own sauna, cold
plunge, basketball court. I've basically
set everything up where I don't have to
leave the house at all anymore. And I
think this is awesome. And we're not
leaving. We're not leaving until we
don't [__] turn $1,000 into $100,000.
That's right. Until $100,000. Well,
you're not leaving there. We got to hold
ourselves accountable for the mistakes
that I did. I made a mistake by falling
asleep last night. Have you heard of The
Punisher? The Punisher? The the show?
You didn't know what the Punisher is? I
know. I know what a punish is. I don't
know what the Punisher. Well, I have
something called The Punisher. Okay. So,
it's it's a you thing. Yeah, it's an us
thing now. Us thing now. Okay. So,
whenever I do something wrong, we both
pay the price. Okay. What's the price
that we have to pay?
Welcome.
I know. I know. You're already sweating,
bro. Yeah. I can turn on the AC. Yeah.
Go ahead.
Go ahead,
bro. I don't remember the last time. I
think it's been 6 months since I turned
this. Six months. And you think it's
going to turn just like that? Yeah. I
honestly think we haven't turned it on
since hundreds of the mill. It's
hundreds of the mill, bro. [__]
insane. All right, we got to jump start
it. Let me know when you're ready. Go.
You're [__] breaking. Oh, I have the
E brake on. Sorry. I think it's been 6
months since I've turned on the
Punisher. This is what we get, brother.
Oh, this is what I get. But we're both
paying the price for not
waking up last night. All right. I see
you're sweating already. Yeah. All
right. So, you're understanding how this
just sucks. It does indeed. We could be
in a Rolls-Royce right now or a Bugatti,
but we're in here. And that's okay.
There will be better days. We learn from
our mistakes. Set and forget. That's
right.
[Music]
[__] Come on.
We got to push it back.
All right. So, we're here. We're going
to get David some shoes. So, David
pulled up to my house, and he's been
here for about a week and a half, and
he's only I've only seen him wear one
pair of shoes. Like, guess why? Why? Cuz
I only have one pair of shoes. Really?
Uh-huh. You don't have any other shoes?
Huh? Okay. We're going to get you a pair
of shoes today, bro. Come on. cuz you
know we we're going to start playing
basketball every single night for
cardio. So he starts getting shredded
and you can't wear your going out shoes,
your gym shoes, the everything and your
basketball shoes and the go to the
chicken shoes and the I got everything.
I got you, bro. Those look identical to
the ones you have, bro. The [__] Like
these look like the upgraded of those,
bro. I don't want all those. I'm not
like a person that like all those
colors, though. No, no. I I I wouldn't
expect for you to be either. I'm just
saying these look literally identical.
We could get you these and we can get
you We'll get you another pair. We'll
get you to these on another two pairs.
Yeah. Should I buy one exotic pair? Like
exotic pair? I mean, rather than you got
to wear them with whatever you want. I
was you, I would get something for like
more casual cuz like right now to go
out, let's say we get invited to go out
with someone. Uhhuh. You're going to
wear those? No, I shouldn't. No, you
should get some like some nice
pairs, right? Yeah. I don't have these.
I'm going to get these right now. We
could get matching if you want. I mean,
that would be kind of gay. That would be
kind of gay. It's only gay if you make
it gay. Yeah. What's the problem with
this? Nothing. Oh, no. Let's get it. I'm
supportive if you are any. No, for sure.
Support the LGBT
community for sure.
[Music]
All right, we got to get
How many you going to get? Just one? No,
we're going to get two. So, my dog has a
passion passion for eating vase.
Passion. A burning desire. Like my dog
will kill itself to take a bite out of a
ball. And almost had done a couple times
already. So he's he I think he's
successfully eaten 10 balls. Not for
like total total probably like 10 balls.
I've come here five different times.
Every single time I come I get two
balls. It's about don't last a week.
Last time you did it they didn't even
last Yeah. It didn't last a weekend.
[Music]
Trade update. Trade update. All right.
So, right now it's 9:37 at night. 9:37
p.m. We are Oh, well, you guys already
saw the trade update. Trade update.
We're up $789.
You want to know what's [__] up, bro?
Literally, the trade that we took
yesterday, which is GBP CAD. Let's just
forget about the fact that that we took
the loss, right? Whatever. Put that
behind. Let's say we entered the trade
here how I should have on that bearish
engulfing. I would have continued to
hold to this point right here where we
technically I would have probably held
all the way to here. We'd be up at 1
to4. So I would be up about $6,000. I
would have closed that position at
$6,000 in profit and then I would have
entered AUD CAD and AUD CAD. I would
have probably not entered here.
Honestly, I would have probably been
waiting for the real pullback to enter.
But the fact that I predicted EuroGBP
the push, the fact that I predicted the
GBP CAD, the second push, the fact that
I predicted AUD CAD the push and GBP and
you do the push and we're only up $700
[__] dollars. That's crazy. You know
what the worst part is? [__] What?
No. No. Every single person watching us
has been getting more money. I've been
making more money than this. Yeah. You
know, it's okay. It's part of the
process. I'm not mad. I understand that
this is the my responsibility in this
industry to show people that this is
possible. I I definitely believe this is
possible. We should be up right now like
at least 7 at least 7 $8,000 to be 100%
legit. But it's okay. We'll take our 700
bucks and we'll move on. For now, we're
going to hold AUD CAD. We have created a
very strong rejection from this area of
interest. Daily time frame seems like
it's having a very strong bearish
engulfing pull down. So, right now, if
we're up 700 here, by the time we make
it over here, according to my
calculations, we'll be around $3,000. In
the meantime, we're making that money.
We're going to ball these [__]
out. You're lucky I'm sore, bro, cuz I
did legs 2 days ago. No, bro. You want
to see how I'm walking right now? Like
bro, we did it again in under 24 hours.
We would be probably at $10,000 if I
would have held you.
[__] You got it.
Who's there?
This is turning into some [__] right
now, bro. For real. Like, I'm not even
mad anymore. I'm not even going to This
is some [__] So, we literally just
got margin called right now. The first
position, bro. So, our first position,
AUD CAD, just got margin called and I
wish we would have caught it live.
Literally, it happened 2 minutes ago.
But basically, price just had this
ridiculous pullback. So, look at this.
We have the left headed right shoulder.
Yesterday, we had the strong break as
we're playing basketball. We're
literally down here. And I anticipated a
quick retest of this area. And I was
actually interested in adding a position
right now to sell. But I said, you know
what? Let me wait. Because I saw that
there was news happening today at 8:30
in the morning with USD, but I did not
think it was going to affect AUD CAD. I
did not think it was going to create
such a massive move like this on this
market. And clearly it [__] did for
whatever reason. And now we have pretty
much blown the account again. Yeah. Like
I mean it could still technically reject
that area. And some of you guys are
going to ask, "Oh, why don't you guys go
break even?" Well, we never go break
even. You already know that breaking
even is like us not being okay with
losing. We're totally okay with losing.
And part of the learning. It's It's
literally part of the process. But bro,
we were literally yesterday we were up
1,000 and something. It was almost like
1,200,300.
I mean market update on the other
markets and GBP CAD. So this basically
hit the overall take profit of this area
where I anticipated. We're having a
reaction to the upside. Euro GBP we have
not had the retest to buy. AUD CAD is I
I think we might get a better entry in
here right now. I'm not going to lie.
Daily time frame looks like it's just
going to create as a daily dogee. I
don't think this is going to continue
going up. So we might enter new entries
here. and GBPN ZD just I guess had a
quick break retest here and is now
heading to the downside. Truth be I'm
not even interested in this market
anymore. I'm really just only interested
in AUD CAD and Euro GBP. So AUD CAD
right now looks like it's coming back
up. I'm going to wait for this
candlestick to close to see how it
closes. If it closes with a strong
rejection cuz clearly this is just news,
right? I go to the 15minute. You can see
how this one candlestick engulfves
pretty much this. Yeah, literally like
the last couple of days. So for now
we're down what we lost 300. This is
just week one, brother. So let's just
keep it going. Set them for free. No
other option, right? Set them free up,
brother. 8:30 in the morning. We'll
check back in to see if we enter this
position or not. Market update, boys. So
we're not looking terrible. Not doing
that bad. But my my my energy is just
like [__] Like I was so hyped for all
this, you know. But this is just it's
it's just tested me very early on. I
haven't been tested by the market in a
very long time. I I've been tested, but
I just haven't given enough of a [__]
Now I give a lot of [__] right? But
this is how we're doing right now. So
we're up about 400 bucks. So we're
technically up and we're at break even
right now. So you can see right here
from the market that we are currently
having a very strong rejection from this
area after we created the major
liquidity grab. So this is lally
literally just like a new thing, bro.
It's not even that. It's just literally
them just taking the money. So that's a
liquidity grab. It's a fake out. Um
whatever. Look at this [__] cat
hunting for lizards. She's going to be
hunting that green lizard right there.
You see it? Oh, look. The lizard's back.
Yeah.
What the [__] It's back. You know what
that means? Yeah. You know what that
means, right? What does that mean? You
don't know what that means? No. The
iguana being here. Like, I don't I don't
think you guys understand what this
means for this week. Last week, we ended
off the week with the iguana. There's a
lot of people watching me. Give me the
signal.
And now we started off the week with the
iguana. Every single time the iguana
comes, we make money. Am I right? Am I
wrong? Do we not? In the last challenge,
there was a ginormous iguana outside of
my window throughout the whole
challenge. Whenever the iguana would
pull up, I would win a trade. That one's
very small compared. I'm an old trader.
I'm just beginning. So, I mean, maybe
small profits. Small trader, small
profits. No, the point is that right now
we are around break even of the account.
I was actually going to deposit an extra
300 bucks to then enter the trade with
more risk, but I said, you know what,
let's just enter it here. We're going to
continue to set and forget today.
There's nothing else that we can do. If
trade makes it all the way down here,
which I do anticipate that it could. We
should be up around like 2500 3,000 in
the account. So, the goal still will be
hit, but it's just kind of how we got
there. We got we got we got we've been
rough. Been rough. We got beat up. We
got a little beat up. So, for now, set
and forget. And we'll update you guys in
a couple hours.
So, imagine if I wouldn't have touched
it, you would have missed. Huh?
All right, boys. Trade update.
You know, now we're talking. So, right
now, we are at That looks good. That
looks good. So, we're technically in the
same property we were yesterday when we
were playing basketball. Just like this.
But we hadn't lost. Maybe this is the
key. What? with the keys to play
basketball. You said it yourself. Yeah,
it's the same thing as yesterday. Just
sucks, bro. Like right now, if we didn't
take yesterday's loss, we'd be uh
playing basketball makes a profit.
That's still continuously powdery for
you. That's the secret to success. The
secret. I'm not I'm not doing any
financial advertisement over here. But
so we have here very clean left head,
right shoulder. We came up, retested the
neckline, rejected the EMA after the
ginormous liquidity grab. We had a
continuation move to the downside and
daily time frame looks like it's going
to close very strong and uh that should
continue our bearish move to the
downside for the rest of the week which
is literally doing the exact same move
as GBP CAD. GBP CAD had the strong move.
Now I had the retracement so we could
possibly sell again tonight if we close
on your AUD CAD. And yeah, basically
we're four for four this week. So every
single market we predict has gone in our
direction. We we haven't really caught
any so we're just waiting on that. Aside
from that set and forget market update
is currently 3 p.m. EST. Market's about
to slow down right now. So, we'll
probably hit the sauna right now, a
little bit more basketball, and we'll
check back in later tonight. Yeah, later
tonight. Pre-London session. I forget.
That's first, right? It's three. You do
this again.
It's a It's a mismatch.
Watch this. What do you want? A three.
Do a three. Three. Three from right
there. Give me that. Give me that.
Five. One. One. What do you want? A shot
or a Leo? You can yard. What do you
want? A shot or a Leo? You got to hit
your shoes. Surprise me. Surprise me.
It's the hustle. The hustle. 61. 61.
What do you want? This is game point
right here. It's the seven. Yeah. What
do you want? There you want. Post me up.
Post up. No, I'm good on that.
shot.
You know, like boom. You see? There we
go. Now I cannot go if I want my knees
to stay in place.
Look over here. Big step over here.
It's a hustle.
Almost tied. This is game point, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Wow. Sir, a little bit of
space. No.
Give it a
game. Game. All right, boys. So, market
update for anticipation for London
session. Are you ready for tonight? I'm
ready. You sure you're ready to stay up
tonight? The whole night. The whole
night. Remember, if we don't wake up
tonight for London session, you don't
wake me up if there's something ready in
the market. I know. I know what
happened. It already did happen. I know.
Yeah. We got to drive the beat. You
understand that, right? I got you. Okay.
So, right now, AUD CAD, despite the
[__] wick out or the liquidity or
the margin call, whatever, we got it
into almost the same entry. Right now,
we're up about a,000. Total balance is
1,600. Right now, the structure is being
very strong. We've had a very massive
liquidity grab which took everybody out.
The move continued to happen to the
downside. Left head, right shoulder,
retest a neckline sell. I anticipate
that we're going to sell off of this
area here to continue going to the
downside. We might add entries here, but
my intentions are to continue to hold
GBP CAD. Despite us predicting the whole
entire move, we somehow still managed to
have a massive retracement to the
upside. I don't love this daily price
action, but I might have an interest in
selling from this structure level here.
4hour time frame is pulling up to this
area of interest. If I get some
rejections here, how we did here, I'm
going to be interesting in then
potentially selling. And then lastly is
going to be Euro GBP, which we have a
strong inverted head and shoulders.
We're going to wait for the retest of
this neckline along with the EMA for us
to have the price head to the upside.
This looks like a trade for next week,
not going to lie, but it is very strong
nonetheless. So, for now, set and
forget. Set your alarm for like 1 in the
morning, 3:00 in the morning. I'll put
1, two, and three just in case. 1, two,
and three. If GBP CAD gives us some
rejections from this area, wake me up. I
got you. And if AUD CAD gives us some
strong rejections from this structure
point right here, like I discloses an
engulfing or any strong rejections, you
know what you're looking for. Wake me
up. If not, you got it. But if not, just
let me sleep and then you can stay awake
to that. Okay. All right. Trade update
in 3 2 1. All right. So, trade update.
Right now, it's 10:14 at night. So, the
trade that we were anticipating earlier
has officially hit our full take profit
zone. So, hit our takeprofit for our
point right here. And we're all 2,300 on
the account. We're going to close all
the positions right now. I'm not home.
I'm not with the GK having the barbecue
with the boys. GK Kid stayed home and
we're going to close all the positions
live right now for 2,300. Close right
here. All the positions live operations.
Close all positions. Done. Boom. Trade
update closed. Check back in in an hour.
I'm doing good. Doesn't matter. So, we
woke you up. He He fell asleep a little
bit early so you can wake up for London.
You still might have to wake up for
London. That's fine. Just letting you
know. Trade update. So, you guys saw
that I just closed it at the barbecue I
was at. So, just show you guys, you
know, better quality. Close the account.
Close the trade at 2,300 in profit. So,
this is where we are right now in the
account on 2300. So, let me show you
guys how it's looking. AUD CAD basically
from my last trade update. It had a
beautiful rejection from this area
exactly where I was potentially looking
to add a position but was out of session
so I didn't hit my take profit to the
tea. Like look at that. That is
literally to the pip. That is perfection
at its finest. And I actually closed it
a little bit above here. Less than what
I wanted to originally but fine. No big
deal. We got out where we should have
and trade is complete. Now, I'm going to
be waiting for some retracements to
potentially sell, even enter more cells.
GBP CAD, as of right now, has not gave
us the rejection from here that we
wanted to. So, we're going to place an
alarm here for once it breaks and retest
under to then sell. Euro GBP, we're
still waiting for the retracement back
into this area. And GBP NZD is having a
very strong rejection here, which we
might enter a trade tonight in London
session. So, this candlestick is going
to close in the next hour and a half.
So, that's going to be at 1:00 in the
morning, right? If that candlestick
closes like that, how it is right now,
1:00 in the morning, you [__] call
me, brother. No, don't pull the door
down. Don't worry. Trust me, we cannot
miss another [__] trade. The goal for
the week was to be at 3,000. Okay, we're
close, though. Yeah. Yeah, we're at
2,300. If we never lost that original
trade at first, that 300. I know. We We
would be at 3,000. We wouldn't have
wicked out. I know. We would be like
almost a 10 cuz we it was like six then
this 2,300. We'll be we're looking good.
If we would have closed the first trade
at like 5,000 in profit, I would have
risked the full 5,000 plus the one. So,
we'd probably be like at 15. Yeah,
that's insane. Like 15 17,000. But you
know what? It's okay. It's fine. No big
deal. Right now, it's 11:30 at night.
We're going to be waiting for London
session to kick in. And yeah, so I'm
going to shower now and I'll see you
there. Yeah, if it's ready. If it's
ready. Yeah. So, if you get a strong
rejection from this candlestick right
here, you let me know. and the AUD CAD
if it retests this area here like if I
doubt it's going to do it but if it has
a nice pullback into this area to then
retest the neckline of this head and
shoulders right here you know this left
head right shoulder so kind of like this
area right here I'm going to have my
alarm set up to do just in case I'm
going to put an alarm right around here
to let me know and if GBPNZD closes
below this right here then I will
potentially be interested in selling All
right let's do it good night for me for
you and then let me know all I got you
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Market update right now 2:16 in the
morning. And would you look at that? No
missed calls. David
David lost a lot of weight. Where's
David? Guess what happened? David didn't
[__] wake up. And this is going to
cost him. I had an idea to wake him up
with. We have big ass fireworks that
were left over from New Year. We're
going to put him inside the room. Me and
thought about it. We probably kill him.
They they'll literally explode the whole
entire house. So, we're going to wake
him up in a bit more exciting way. But,
nonetheless, trade update. Market did
exactly as I said. Right now, we are up
about 1,700 bucks. So, almost 100% of
what we decided to take. So, market
trade update. We had price pull up to
this area. We got a ginormous dogee
rejection candle. This took exactly what
I wanted for us to enter the trade. So,
David was supposed to call me at 1:00 in
the morning to take this trade. Guess
what? He didn't. I was taking a shower
at that time and I saw the trade close
like that. I took the trade immediately
and waited for his call. But he never
woke up. He would have missed out on
this opportunity. This is the exact same
[__] that happened to us on GBP CAT. So
if you look at GBP CAT, GBPCAT literally
pulled right back up to the exact same
level I had to push. Like I could have
easily taken GBP CAD here, which would
have been my revenge for this. But you
know what? I was liking more the
technicals on GBP NZD and update on AUD
CAD and price is just continuing to go
to the downside. But this has created
our perfect entry confirmation right
here on the 1 hour. Beautiful 1 hour
bearish engulfing candlestick. We
entered the trade right after this
2-hour dogee wick fill and it's a great
trade. Honestly, great trade. Everything
is looking decent. We're about to double
up. About to be 100% in profit. Just our
boy David didn't wake up. Let's go wake
him up, shall we? All right. So, he he's
in the other house over there. But this
is what we're going to use. We're going
to
We're up two fucking,000. David, he
decided to fall asleep and not wake up
and wake me up for this. I had to wake
myself up. I I thought I counted on you,
brother. So, now we're going to wake you
up.
What happened, bro? You were supposed to
wake up for London, brother. What time
is it, bro? This
Bro, it's 2:30 in the morning, bro.
Let's go. You were You were supposed to
wake me up. Wow.
[Laughter]
Whoa. We I got into the trade, right?
You got into Yeah. So, look. So, we're
up 1,900 on the account.
Brother, look at this. You're supposed
to wake me up as soon as we get that
4hour rejection candlestick. What What
pair are we on? GBNZD. Okay. I didn't
see that one, brother. What happened,
bro? Now you got to do something now.
Now, now we got to figure out what he's
got to do to make up for his for himself
not being um
accountable.
I'm not driving fast. 24. No, that's not
hard enough. No, you got to do something
then. You got to pay the price. Well,
honestly, you can go back to sleep now.
Okay, cuz I already entered the trade,
so it's all good. So, right now, trade
update. We're rejecting this area very
nicely. And uh yeah, that's pretty much
it. Good night. Good night. See you. All
right. So, back in the office. So, we
woke up David. Honestly, just for the
content, we really didn't have to do
that. Honestly, you know, I I could
probably close right now. Should I close
right now? I mean, has it hit your take
profit? Yeah, the No, the goal for the
week was $3,000. So, we're way above our
goal. Yeah, that's your goal for the
week, but your take profit in the trade.
No, the take profit in this trade will
put us at about $8,000. Brother, I don't
[__] forget. You're right. I don't
forget. Good night. Let's hope tomorrow
we wake up and we're not out of break
even.
This is [__] [__] bro. You
decided, bro, you decided to fall asleep
last night, bro. And that [__] almost
cost us [__] $2,000, bro. Imagine.
Yeah, you almost [__] the whole thing
up, bro. Exactly. So, trade update right
now. It's 9:30 in the morning. But we I
I think we were up at this at one
[__] point, like $4,000, bro. I was
knocked out. Yeah. Trade update right
now. So GBP CAD, funny enough, bro, this
trade, this [__] trade is literally
doing the same thing as last time when
it took us out and gives us opportunity
came back and it just rejected again.
Like I could have just entered this
trade right now again. I just don't have
that type of opportunity because I'm
still holding this position, right? Euro
GBP just this this thing just rocketed.
It never stopped. AUD CAD had the
pullback exactly how I anticipated into
this area and is now having a sell-off.
And then lastly, GBP NZD. So yesterday
after we entered the trade, we just
continued to hold and the trade
continued to have a push to the
downside. So right now, from the looks
of it, bro, I hate to be this guy and
say this, but I I believe it's going to
have a push to the upside. I I literally
believe it's going to have a full-blown
retracement and like go back into like
breaking up. I just don't believe that
the daily has enough momentum to keep it
going, bro. What do What do you think?
I'm starting to guess scared not to. I
mean, the daily timer 10 has a strong
daily dogee. Like, that's good, but it's
not enough. I mean, bro, we can do some
DJ [__] right? Hear me out. Hear me
out. All right, it's day four turning
a,000 into 100,000 and we got to do some
DJ [__] right now. We have a decision to
make before the market closes that can
change [__] everything. Are you down?
You know, I'm always down.
Sounded kind of sus. All right, so we
could potentially close GBPMZD right now
and enter what? And then enter GBP CAT
cuz technically we would be at our goal
for the week, right? And the thing is, I
don't know if these opportunities are
going to be this hot next week, you
know? So, if they're hot this week, I
want to take advantage of it this week.
So, we would close this position right
here at about $2,000 in profit and then
we would enter this one immediately. I
do believe this is going to have a
strong pullback, honestly. And I don't
think that it would make sense to
continue holding this operations close.
There you go. As of right now, you guys
can see here we have our next closed
position, GBP NZD, for an extra 2,000.
And right now the account is sitting at
4,300. So we're going to immediately
jump into this other [__] cell,
right? GBP CAD, we're getting our
revenge. You think what you did to me
was funny, huh? You think what you did
to me was funny? No. No, it didn't do it
to me. It did it to to us. You and I.
You and I. Mhm. To you and me thing
here. Laughing to the both of us at the
same time. What? Uh I I I think we
should just call it a week, bro.
Honestly, dude, we just turned $1,000
into 4,300, bro. In like a day. So, I
think we're going to call it a week
here, boys. Now, we're going to set and
forget. And we should do something
today. We should get out the house, bro.
We haven't really gotten out at all. You
should have done it, bro. Yeah. You
should have taken the [__] trade,
man. Look at this. It's okay. It
happens. But you want to know what
happened? A bigger mistake happened. The
GBPZD trade that we have taken, we have
to officially disqualify it. We had to
withdraw the profits that we made from
GBPNZD because we did not send that out
in the WhatsApp and Telegram. And the
way this challenge works is every single
trade that I take inside of the
challenge, I have to share with you guys
completely for free. If I don't share
it, I cannot take the trade. So, let me
show you guys here the Telegram channel
where we're going to be sharing all of
the trades, which by the way, the link
for you guys to follow this journey is
in the bio. You can join the WhatsApp or
Telegram where we're literally sharing
and giving all these trades completely
for free. Right. This morning I updated
that we had GVPN ZD the explanation of
it. Last night I did a video. We sent it
right around 10 p.m. EST explain the
markets I'm interested in trading and
the breakdown of it. And then I realized
here I only sent AUD, GBP, and EuroGP. I
did not send GBP NZD. If you notice here
in the morning I did AUD, GBP, Eurogp,
but NZD. I [__] up. We did. We We
[__] up. We [__] up. So, you [__]
up by not waking up. I [__] up by not
sending the trade that was executed that
night. So, I thought about it and we
asked the people in our community. And
the simplest solution to it is simply
withdraw. Withdrawing the profits that
we made on GBPNZD for about how much was
it? It was like 19 something. Like 19
like 19 almost $2,000. We're going to
withdraw that money. And then as soon as
we withdraw it, then what we do is we
just pretend like we never took that
trade. Yes. Keep going from there. And
we keep going from the 2,300 for that
update. GVPND. So we actually close up
here at that line. So we would actually
probably made like an extra $3,000,
which ultimately would have not mattered
because since we did not send the trade,
it's not going to count. We would have
to just withdraw more. That's it. Which
is fine, right? Free money. But it it
[__] up like our psychology because we
see more money on the Metatrader
account. Whatever. AD CAD slowing down.
You're a GP. nothing GBP had having the
exact push from the area how we've been
anticipating. This is uh where you're
going to be facing all of next week.
Okay, good. All right. So, just letting
you know. So, we're going to go into our
client portal. Total right now we have
in the account 4,363.
This is the G challenge and we're going
to withdraw. All right. So, this is
total amount 1,976.
So, we withdraw those profits and that
puts us back at the account balance that
we had before we took GPND. This is
showing you guys how transparent and how
legit we're making this challenge. Like
if if it were to be somebody else, it'
be like, "Ah, you know what? Let's count
it or let's" They wouldn't even have
addressed it to begin with. Exactly.
They were just like, "Ah, whatever." But
us, there you go. Success. Withdraw.
Successful. And then our actual balance
is 2387. Yeah, it shows right there.
Yeah, it shows right there. 2387.
Perfect. All right. All right. So, that
being said, that's market update at 1
p.m. Let's see where today takes us. All
right, boys. Market update. It's 3:00
p.m. EST. So, the market is pretty much
slowing down after having the head and
shoulders.
Let's go run some errands that we got to
do today again. But today is uh going to
be a little bit more humiliating for
both of us. You know what? You deserve
this because I made a mistake and he
made a mistake. We're paying for it
together. My name's Megan.
These fans of mine have got some stories
to tell. Seen parts of heaven and a
whole lot of hell. Headed west to state
flame in the ground.
[__] out of gas, bro. You have to
push it over here, bro. From where? From
like off the bridge. Hey, bro. Like I I
drove a Bugatti. Do you think like I
want to be doing this? But it looks like
it since you want to be not sending
trace to the community. It's my fault
holding myself responsible.
[Music]
All right. So, we're in Brickle. So,
usually I I literally park in the same
parking spot my Bugatti and we're here
in the Vito. Yeah. So, I mean, I know,
but technically, you know, we did make
some Oh, look. I just got an alarm.
Look. GBP CAD 413 alarm. Let's see what
happened. Okay. Look. So GBP CAD right
now is having a retest of that neckline
and the daily time frame has closed with
a basically exactly what I anticipate.
Well, it's about a close of that daily
dogee. So we're still good. We still
have an opportunity to make some money
before the weekend and we kind of just
come out here to chill because we
technically followed our plan. Yeah. But
we got to come in the Punisher because
we technically did. Also, it's like a
balance. It's a balance. Correct. Have
you ever been to Bickl? No. show you
around a little bit and hopefully we go
home before traffic or we'll probably
hit a workout somewhere here and we go
back home.
[Music]
Bro, those look fire. Those look fire.
Fire.
Oh, bro. Those are the ones, bro. Those
are the ones. Those are the ones. Those
are the ones, bro.
Jeez, that's the secret sauce right
there. You guys don't know this is where
the Ooh,
you know, you know. But we're going to
take some coconuts together.
Ooh. So, sometimes being outside having
fun, this happens to us, right? So, this
is uh and we're supposedly being
punished. I know, right? We're supposed
to be punished so we're not going to
make the mistake again. But usually
going getting away, we [__] up cuz
we're not in front of the computer. I'm
I'm not going to lie. This has been an
extremely volatile week, right? No. No.
I've I've I've noticed like we have like
20 different entries that and that
usually does not happen. Every single
entry has happened like to perfection.
No. Yeah. We we called it every single
one. Every single one has gone the same
way that we predicted. Technically, we
haven't lost a trade. Exactly.
Technically, because I consider a lost
trade when we say something's going to
go up and it goes down. So, let me show
you guys what's going on. Right. So, as
of right now, 10:07 at night, trade
update. Still no new trades. GBP CAD. We
anticipated a perfect reaction from this
area to sell. Price retested it. Sold
exactly how we anticipated. It's just
[__] crazy how we didn't enter it.
Not going to lie, we would have not
entered it one because we were out of
the office. Not saying we don't take
trades out of the office, but we were
just we're not in the environment and we
also weren't in the session. Like that
happened at 7:00 p.m. EST. To me, all I
care is New York, London. I don't care
Asia, Tokyo, Japan.
So, we completely avoided this win,
which is never really a good thing. Next
is Euro GBP. Price never retested how we
wanted to. So, we never took the trade.
AUD CAD. This is [__] insane. This is
the trade that we entered up here and
then it had to push to our takerit. And
I' I've been explaining to you guys,
this trade is massively bullish and we
can expect more move to the downside.
And look at that. We missed out on
basically doubling our profit by simply
setting and forgetting. And you know
what? It's okay because I believe this
trade is setting up a very strong trade
for next week. So weekly time frame is
closing very bearish. Daily time frame
very bearish. This trade is a big trade
for next week. And lastly is GBP NZD. So
we were in these sells. We closed the
position and after we closed it, look at
that. It would have came back and tooken
us at a loss if we would have
hypothetically held all the way to this
takerit here, which truthfully, but we
didn't, right? We closed a little bit
earlier. Out of all these markets right
now, there's only one that we're
interested in taking. It's going to be
GBPZD for tonight. I got you. I you
don't even have to mention it. You got
to wake up tonight. I got you. All
right. I I already So what happened was
I was I was telling him that the rookie
mistake that I did and I mean of course
everybody has done it. You know when you
set the alarm to be like at 6:00 in the
morning and you don't wake up at 6:00 in
the morning cuz the alarm never sounded
cuz the alarm was at P.M. Exactly.
That's what happened to me. That's what
happened. So you I mean I put the alarm
at PM. So of course it didn't sound.
It's not that I didn't wake up. It's
that nothing woke me up. I think
something woke you up, you I mean, that
that's different. That's different. Kind
of sucks, too. I'm not going to lie. Now
that I said it that way. The point is
that if you don't wake up tonight, let's
say we're going to have another
strategic way on how to wake you up.
Only if like you can wake up, wake me up
only if GBP NZD somehow manages to come
back into this area in order to give us
an entry. Right? So, this trade
technically already happened. I want to
basically enter this exact same trade
right here. So right now the 4 hour time
frame having a massive bearish engulfing
candlestick. This candlestick closes in
2 and 1/2 hours. If when this closes and
then around 1 2 in the morning we start
pulling back up. I'm going to
potentially be interested in selling. So
right now it's just being extremely
volatile and I'm going to put my alarm
at the high of this candlestick right
here in order for me to be notified. So
if it were to pull back we'll be
entering. Okay.
We're looking for sells and everything
else is pretty much cooked. That is the
market update. 10 p.m. EST.
I'll see you in the morning. Well, if
anything, you wake me up at night. Mhm.
All right, boys. So, we're going to do a
trade up to today in David's office.
Technically, my office, cuz I left it to
David. I'm just I'm just leasing it for
now. This is my favorite office. I'm not
going to lie. Like, when I actually like
do [__] this is where I spend the
majority of my life. I I understand why.
All right. So, right now it's 400 p.m.
EST as you guys can clearly see.
Usually, we would do the trade updates a
little bit earlier, but honestly, last
night David was basically trading
London. I was up as well a little bit
just kind of being there making sure
that the trade was going to present
itself and obviously luckily we decided
to avoid that loss. And this is the
basically what happened last night. So
while we were waiting for this trade to
have this break and retest of this area,
price never gave me some continuation
momentum. So as we're watching this
trade last night, we just kept watching
it trickle up, trickle up, trickle up,
and we just basically avoided this trade
as a whole. AUD CAD last night had
pretty much a consolidation around the
bottom here after this massive push.
Euro GBP did end up having some
accumulation in a little bit break and
retest under, but truthfully, we're not
really that interested in it. until next
week. And GP CAD was honestly the
monster where it just continue
plummeting to the downside after and
then having a little bit of retracement.
So no trade last night. No, we did not.
How did it feel to stay up and not do
anything? Just be looking at the
computer all night. How did that feel? I
mean, I didn't feel anything at all like
to be honest. No, no. I mean, it was it
was like interesting to be how London
actually moves, but like the fact that
we didn't do a trade, nothing. Okay. I
mean, good cuz that like the quicker you
normalize that the better, right? Cuz
it's going to be like the more you do
it, the more tired you get. Like I'm
tired right now. I felt like I slept 2
hours last night. I woke up today at
like 9:30, 10 in the morning, and now
it's kind of when I'm like going to need
that midday nap again. But that kind of
like compounds over time. Imagine
staying up every single night. Not
saying you have to, but imagine staying
up every single night for the whole
entire week. Like that kind of builds
up. That's that makes a compound
interest there. So, a lot of people are
curious on our risk management plan for
the challenge, right? because next week
is you. Yeah. And you want to kind of
know what you should be aiming for and
that's right be rating for. So this week
technically we turned 600 bucks into
2,300 because we took the loss and we
reentered around 600 bucks. We aim to
have a 1 to2 1 to 2.5 risk-to-reward.
This is the conservative setup where we
risk anywhere from 60 to 80%. And we
look to pretty much double/2.5 every
single week. We just need technically
four more weeks with four more winning
trades at a 1 to two point 1 to 2.5 risk
reward. Or the little bit more
aggressive slashconservative.
It could be a 1 to3 risk-to-reward/1 to4
where then we would risk the same 60 80%
but we're just targeting more
riskreward. Bro, next week we're going
to [__] do this, bro. All right.
That's what the [__] I'm saying. All
right. That's [__] right. Yeah.
Squeeze hard, bro. Squeeze. You squeeze
hard. No, you squeeze hard. You squeeze
hard. You have a you have a bigger hand.
Doesn't mean that I'm stronger. With
that being said, ladies and gentlemen,
make sure to
follow the journey. No. Set it for set
and forget too. Set and forget, too. No.
You set and forget first and then follow
the journey. And then you follow the
journey. You said this is your first
time in Miami, right? Uh-huh. You've
never been out of a boat in Miami. In
Miami or in the whole world? I mean,
you've never been on a boat at all.
Mm-m. Are you scared of the water? What
the [__] I mean, we're going to be on
top of the boat, right? So, but are you
scared of the water in general? No. No.
Huh? How do you know if you've never
been out in a boat? Cuz I mean, I don't
know. But I don't think so. I don't I I
don't really think I'll be scared. You
know how to swim? Yeah. Do you've been
in the water before? In a pool? Let's
find out. Before we go out on the boat,
we have some duties. We got to take out
our eggs. Make sure that we have
breakfast for tomorrow. I have about 25
chickens here. Every single day, we
probably got 30 eggs. Honestly,
[Laughter]
[Music]
Is it the first time out on the boat?
How is it? Good.
Where are your shorts? told me to wear
pants. Who told you to wear pants, bro?
I don't remember who it was, but
somebody told me to wear pants. Guy's
living a life. He's living his best
life, bro. Look at this guy.
[Music]
Let it go, baby. Let it
go.
How did this happen?
[Music]
Yo, I was like, what the [__] is going
on, bro?
What's good? What's good, my boy? What's
going on? How you feel, bro? I drove
right and I saw the boat and I saw your
hair. Your luscious hair.
Yeah, of course. Of course, G.
Congratulations, G. You're lucky. I
applied to the same thing, too. Hey, yo,
bro. It's like I always see you out
here, bro. You just living your best
life, bro. I'm trying to get like you. I
mean, bro, you're living your best life.
You're out here, bro. Hey, but this is
my job, though. I'm trying to be on the
boat vibing. I'm trying to own it. Hey,
but listen, you're a big expiration.
Everybody always tells you. You know
what I'm saying? But I just wanted to
tell you, I trade as well. You know what
I'm saying? And watching your [__] bro,
it's like, [__] Yeah. You know, seven
years ago, you know what I'm saying?
What was I really doing? I was doing
that. You know, you same thing as you.
You was doing Doug and Dutton. I'm like,
damn, bro. If he can do it, walking. Of
course. Yeah. Of course. So, I just
wanted to give you a little show, man. I
appreciate you know. Hey guys, keep
grinding. Keep pushing, bro. Don't ever
give up. I promise you it's not that
hard. It's simple, right? But it's it's
a little bit complex cuz all you got to
do is do the same [__] every day. That's
the important part. That's the hard
part, right? Because when you don't want
to do it, it's hard to do it. That's
where discipline comes in. This man
ain't do all this [__] just because he
had the motivation, man. [__]
motivation. Do that [__] because you got
to lock in. You got to do it. Listen,
this is what say I always say if you
don't lock in, you going to have to
clock in. Yo, yo, yo. Yo, you speaking
some real [__] It's facts because at
the end of the day, you do not want to
die. You don't want to be on your
deathbed saying, "Bro, what if I would
have just gave it a shot? What if I
would have just been like, "Fuck, let me
just go all in." Because at the end of
the day, the same people that's having
opinions with you now, they gonna be in
the same death bed with you later, and
they gonna be like, "Fuck, having the
same thoughts. What if I would have done
it?" So, at the end of the day, bro,
just do you. [__] do what you
got to do because listen, the worst case
is that we start at square one, regular,
working a regular job. My job ain't that
regular, but listen, I'm blessed. I did
uh I'm not like Alex. I'm trying to get
like Alex. And listen, bro, we all going
to get there one day. Don't compare
yourself. Comparison is the thief of
joy. Just be grateful for where you at.
Thank God every day. You know what I'm
saying? And listen, if you got something
you want to work towards, keep working
towards it. Don't worry about just keep
working towards that, bro. I promise
you, it's going to work out because all
you got to do is believe in yourself.
You know what I'm saying? If you can't
believe in yourself, how you going to
expect the next man to believe in you,
you know what I'm saying? Most people
don't even believe in themselves. So,
you can't do that either. But other than
that, y'all have a great day. Much love.
vlog. Y'all keep doing your thing. Alex,
yo, you already know, man. Keep doing
your thing. Camera, man. I be peeping
you, too, man. Y'all be grinding, bro.
Hey, I got to shake your hand, bro. Hold
on. In all seriousness, bro. Appreciate
you, man. Listen, bro. I know it. I know
it's get hectic out here. It's Miami.
You feel me? Don't let these people get
to you. Obviously, they're just mad that
they are worthy of you. That's what it
is, bro. You already know. But listen, I
appreciate you. Of course, man. The
thing about it is that people praise you
when you already made it. They don't
praise you when you need to get back
there. But at the end of the day, we can
never forget what we carry. You got the
right mindset, bro. You got the right
drive. Just keep it going, bro. I'll see
you over here, brother. Yeah. Hell yeah.
Yes, you will. Take care, bro. Hey,
congratulations. Have a great day. Enjoy
your night. Take care, brother.
He says some facts. What' he say? If you
don't lock in, you're going to you're
going to [__] clock in, bro. That was
really [__] that guy just said. Look at
this guy. He's he's he's seasick right
now. He's like stuck right there.